Finding Aid of the Midwest Archives Conference Records, 1972-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1972-2014, UWM Manuscript Collection 194; 42.1 cubic ft. (112 boxes) 1,083 digital files (171 MB)
  - 4. Council, 1972-2013
    - Council Meetings, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
    - Council Meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 115, Folder 23-25)
    - Council Meetings, 1999-2001 (Box 50, Folder 3-5)
    - Council Meetings, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Council Meetings, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Council Meetings, 2004-2009 (Box 116, Folder 2-6)
    - Council Meetings, 2010-2013
      Records are arranged by date of in-person Council meetings at the annual meeting (in spring) and symposium (fall). Records of Council meetings that occur between these meetings are arranged separately.
      Minutes of the Annual Members' Meeting can also be found in the Spring meeting folders for 1994-2007.
  - 5. Committees, 1972-2010
    This subgroup includes records from numerous committees. Most of the records consist of correspondence; committee guidelines, reports, and procedures; meeting minutes; and committee membership lists. The primary focus of many of these committees was the planning and evaluating of the bi-annual meetings. This subgroup also contains Nomination Committee materials and information pertaining to MAC elections and members, as well as Scholarship Committee files, which document the development of scholarships. The Twenty-fifth Anniversary Committee files primarily consist of e-mail messages between committee members, but also contain information pertinent to the history and founding of MAC. Records of the Local Arrangements and Program Committees are arranged in record subgroup 6.
    - Ad Hoc Personnel Procedures Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Advertising Task Force, 2002-2003 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Archie Motley Scholarship Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Archives Committee
      - 1972-1981 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - 1992-1995 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Personnel Matters, 1976-1978 (Box 51, Folder 4-5)
    - Conservation Committee, 1972-1981 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Constitutional Revision Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Coordinating Committee, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Development Task Force, 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Education Committee, 1979-1987 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Education Committee, 1987-1992 (Box 117, Folder 2-3)
    - Education Committee, 1992-1995 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Education Committee, 1993-1997 (Box 117, Folder 4-7)
    - Education Committee, 1999 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Education Committee, 2003-2008 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Education Committee, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Education Committe Reports, 1991-1995 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Education Task Force, 2010 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Emeritus Membership Committee, 1979-1992 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Emeritus Membership Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Emeritus Membership Committee, 2001-2008 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Emeritus Membership Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Governing Structures Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 52, Folder 4-5)
    - International Initative, 1991-2002 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Invested Reserves Planning Committee, 1989-1995 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Investment Advisory Committee, 1998 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Liability Insurance Task Force, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Logo Redesign Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Louisa Bowen Memorial Scholarship Committee, 1998-2009 (Box 112, Folder 2-3)
    - Meeting Coordinating Committee, Meeting Manual, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Meeeting Issues Task Force, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Meeting Planning Task Force, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Membership Committee, 1973-1981 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Membership Committee, 1984-1994 (Box 52, Folder 12-14)
    - Membership Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Membership Committee, 2003-2007 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Membership Committee
      - Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1983-2003 (Box 53, Folder 2-5)
      - Guidelines, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Members, 1987-2003 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - New Member Packet, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - New Members Dinner, 2000-2003 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Reports to Council, 1998-2003 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Membership Development Committee, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Membership Survey Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Membership Retention Task Force, 2007-2008 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Minority Scholarship Committee, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Minority Scholarship Committee, 2004 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - New Projects Committee, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Newsletter Task Force, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Nominating Committee, 1972-1983 (Box 54, Folder 1-11)
    - Nominating Committee, 1984-1990 (Box 55, Folder 1-7)
    - Nominating Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
    - Nominating Committee, 2003-2009 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Nominating Committee
      - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence with Candidates, 1993-1995 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Election Packets, 1991-2006 (Box 56, Folder 5-6)
    - Personnel Procedures Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - President's Award Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 56, Folder 8-9)
    - President's Award Committee, 1989-1997 (Box 57, Folder 1-6)
    - Program Analysis Committee, 1973-1979 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Scholarship Committees, 1992-1997 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Special Projects Committee, Seminar on Regional Archival Systems, 1974-1975 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Steering Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
    - Task Force on Archives and Society, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Task Force on Educational Goals, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Task Force to Review Constitution and By-Laws, 1992-1994 (Box 118, Folder 14-15)
    - Technology Task Force, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Teller Subcommittee, 1989, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 9-10)
    - Thirty-Fifth Anniversary Committee, 2007 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Committee
      - Banquet, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Chronicle, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Emeritus and Founding Members, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Financial, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Gift and Giveaways, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - History, 1996-1997 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Hospitality Area and Cake, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Local Arrangements and Program Committees, 1996-1997 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Logo and Name Tags, 1996-1997 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Louisa Bowen, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - 6. Meetings, 1972-2014
    This subgroup contains materials pertaining to the spring and fall membership meetings. Files are arranged in chronological order by meeting, and then alphabetically by folder title. Included are Local Arrangement Committee files, Program Committee files, programs, and meeting handouts and packets. The Local Arrangement Committee files include minutes and reports, which document the committee's activities in the host city. Included are materials which document hotel planning, publicity, tours and activities, vendors and exhibits, and AV needs. The Program Committee files include minutes and reports of the committee responsible for planning sessions and contacting speakers. The meeting handouts and packets contain pocket programs, lists of attendees, and information about MAC activities and other activities in the host city. This record subgroup also includes scripts for the Raiders of the Lost Archives programs which MAC members performed at several MAC meetings.
    - Spring 1972
      - Meeting Handouts, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Fall 1972
      - Meeting Handouts, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Spring 1973
      - Meeting Handouts, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Program Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Fall 1973
      - Meeting Handouts (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Program Committee (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Spring 1974
      - Meeting Handouts, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Program Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Fall 1974
      - Meeting Handouts, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Program Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Spring 1975
      - Meeting Handouts, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Program Committee, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Fall 1975
      - Meeting Handouts, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Program Committee, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Spring 1976
      - Meeting Handouts, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Program Committee, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Fall 1976
      - Meeting Handouts, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Program Committee, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Spring 1977
      - Meeting Handouts, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - Program Committee, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Fall 1977
      - Meeting Handouts, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Program Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 2-3)
    - Spring 1978
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Meeting Handouts, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Program Committee, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Fall 1978
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Meeting Handouts, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Program Committee, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Spring 1979
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Meeting Handouts, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Program Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Spring 1980
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Handouts, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Program Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Fall 1980
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Program Committee, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Spring 1981
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 7-8)
      - Meeting Packet, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Program Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Fall 1981
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Meeting Handouts, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Program Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Spring 1982
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Meeting Packet, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Fall 1982
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Final Report, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Packet, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Program Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Program Committee, Publicity, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Program Committee, Sessions, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Spring 1983
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - Final Report, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 9)
        - Program, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 10)
        - Publicity, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Meeting Packet, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Program Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 12-13)
    - Fall 1983
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - 1982-1983 (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - Final Report, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 2)
        - Program, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 3)
        - Publicity, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - Raiders of the Lost Archives, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Local Arrangements Committee and Program Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Fall 1983, Meeting Handouts, 1983 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Spring 1984
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 9)
        - Final Report, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 10)
        - Meeting Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 11)
        - Program/Registration Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Meeting Packet, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Program Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Fall 1984
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Committees, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 65, Folder 15)
        - Photographs, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 16)
        - Program, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Meeting Handouts, 1984 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - Program Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Spring 1985
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - Meeting Packet, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Fall 1985
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Fundraising Correspondence, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Meeting Packet, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Program Committee, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Spring 1986
      - Meeting Packet, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Fall 1986
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 66, Folder 5-6)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Clippings, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Fundraising, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Meeting Handouts, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Program Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Program Committee, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Program Committee
        - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence with Program Participants, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 4)
        - Final Report, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 5)
        - Grant, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 6)
        - Microfilming Workshop, 1985-1986 (Box 67, Folder 7)
        - Session Topics, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Raiders of the Lost Archives, II, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Spring 1987
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Publicity, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Meeting Packet, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Program Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
      - Program Committee
        - Correspondence with Program Participants, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - Final Report, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - Publicity, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Fall 1987
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Final Report, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Meeting Handouts, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Program Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Spring 1988
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 12)
        - Final Report, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 1)
        - Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - Publicity, 1986-1988 (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Reception, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Resolutions, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - Vendors, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Meeting Packet, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Program Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Fall 1988
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Final Report, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Meeting Handouts, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Spring 1989
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Final Report, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Meeting Packet, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Fall 1989
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Final Report, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Meeting Packet, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Program Committee, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Spring 1990
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Publicity, 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Meeting Packet, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Program Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Fall 1990
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1987-1990 (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Final Report, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - Meeting Packet, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Spring 1991
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Final Report, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Meeting Packet, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - Program, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Program Committee, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Fall 1991
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Meeting Packet, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - Program, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Program Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Spring 1992
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Final Report, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Meeting Packet, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 16)
      - Program, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Program Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 70, Folder 9-13)
      - Program Committee
        - 20th Anniversary Subcommittee, 1991-1992 (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - Committee Composition, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 71, Folder 3)
        - Plenary, 1991-1992 (Box 71, Folder 4)
        - Session Ideas and Rankings, 1991-1992 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Raiders of the Lost Archives, III, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Fall 1992
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Packet, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 17)
      - Program, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Program Committee, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Spring 1993
      - Meeting Packet, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - Program, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Fall 1993
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 71, Folder 10)
        - Final Report, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 11)
        - Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Meeting Packet, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 19)
      - Program, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Program Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Spring 1994
      - Meeting Packet, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Program, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Program Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 72, Folder 2-3)
      - Program Committee
        - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 4)
        - Final Report, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Fall 1994
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Meeting Packet, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Program, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Program Committee, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Program Committee
        - Program Proposals, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 9)
        - Session Descriptions, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Spring 1995
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Meeting Packet, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Program, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Program Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Fall 1995
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1992-1995 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Meeting Packet, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Program, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Spring 1996
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Meeting Packet, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Program, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Fall 1996
      - Local Arrangements Committee,1994-1996 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Meeting Packet, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Program, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Program Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Spring 1997
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Meeting Packet, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Program, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Program Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 73, Folder 8-9)
      - Program Committee, Round Tables, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Fall 1997
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 3-4)
      - Meeting Packet, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Program, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Program Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Program Committee, Plenary Speaker Carol Bly, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Raiders of the Lost Archives, IV, 1997 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Spring 1998
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Final Report, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Meeting Packet, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Program, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Program Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Fall 1998
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Meeting Packet, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Program, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Spring 1999
      - Meeting Packet, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - Program, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Program Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Program Committee
        - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Fall 1999
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Final Report, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 11)
        - NHC Grant, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 12)
        - Tours, 1998-1999 (Box 75, Folder 13)
        - Vendors and Fundraising, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - Meeting Packet, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 15)
      - Program, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 16)
      - Program Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Spring 2000
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Meeting Packet, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Program, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Program Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 76, Folder 3-8)
    - Fall 2000
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 110, Folder 4-5)
      - Meeting Packet, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Program, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Program Committee, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Spring 2001
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Packet, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Program, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Fall 2001
      - Meeting Packet, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Program, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Spring 2002
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Budget and Fundraising, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 8)
        - Hotel and AV, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 9)
        - Meeting Promotion, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 10)
        - Tours and Transportation, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Meeting Packet, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Program, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Fall 2002
      - Meeting Packet, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Program, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Spring 2003
      - Program, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Fall 2003
      - Program, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Spring 2004
      - Electronic Records, 2004 Spring, Milwaukee
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 2000-2004 (Box 110, Folder 6-16)
      - Meeting Packet, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - Program, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - Program Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Fall 2004
      - Electronic Records, 2004 Fall, Des Moines
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Meeting Packet, 2004 (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - Program, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 20)
      - Program Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Spring 2005